Previously On Friends
일자리 문제는 어떻게 돼가?
How did the job stuff go?
마크가 일자리를 구해줬어
He offered me one
이스라엘산 최고급 술
한잔 해야겠는 걸!
You know what? This calls for a bottle of Israel's finest
The job is in Paris
파리에서 일하는거야
제발 누가 아무 말이나 좀 해봐
Oh, god please somebody say something
그럼 이 일을 받아들이면
파리로 가야하는거야?
So, If you take this job,
You will be moving to Paris?
아니면 출퇴근하느라 전쟁을 하겠지
Or facing a bitch of a commute
나도 정말 큰 일인 건 알아
I know it's huge and it's scary and it's really far far away from you guys
너희하고 멀리 떨어지게
되는 것도 알고...
하지만 이건 나한테
정말 좋은 기회란 말야
But this's such an incredible apportunity for me
And I've already talked to them about our situation with Emma and they said they will do whatever we need to make us feel comfortable
에마에 대한 것도
회사에 얘기했는데
우리가 원하는대로
최선을 다해서 도와주겠대
OK
그래...
우리가 원하는대로
I mean I'll fly back-and-forth they'll fly you out anything we want
내가 왔다갔다 해도 되고
네가 와도 되고
우리 사장은 사무실 내 자리에
새 램프를 들여놔준다던데
My boss said I might be getting a new lamp in my cubicle
그래, 뭐 어떻게든 해보지
All right, we'll work it out
Oh~ thank you, thank you
고마워
yeah, you sure this's what you want?
정말 이 일을 원하는거지?
그런거 같아
I think it is
Ooh~ what's going on?
무슨 일이야?
나 정말 좋은 직장을 갖게 됐어
I got a really incredible job offer
와~ 잘됐다
- hey! Great! All right
- Good for you!
파리에서 하는 일이야
It's in Paris
뭐? 안돼 안돼 안된다구
what? NO NO NO NO NO NO NO NO NO NO NO
Too much is changing. OK? First, Phoebe getting married. Congraturations
갑자기 너무 많이 변하잖아
우선 피비는 결혼했고.. 축하해
쟤네 둘은 교외에 있는
멍청한 집으로 이사나 간대고
and then these two move into a stupid house in stupid suburbs
hey, this afternoon, you said you'd be supportive
아까까지만 해도
너 밀어줄 거라고 했잖아
왔다갔다 하는 거지
난 원래 못믿을 놈이야
Well, it comes and goes. I wouldn't trust it
이건 나한테 정말 중요한 일이야
Look you guys. This's really really important to me
It means a lot if you could try to get on board
너희들이 밀어주면 더 쉬울거야
Of course we can. Congraturations~ Yay~
당연히 밀어줘야지, 축하해~
- 조이~
- 안돼 안돼
- Joey
- No no no no no no
My hugs are reserved for people staying in America
내 마음은 미국에 남는
사람들을 위해 쓸 거야
조이, 내 말 좀...
Joey, it would mean so..
hey no, get that your 'France going' arms away from me
프랑스 가는 사람 팔은
내 몸에 대지 마!
조이...
Joey
너 괜찮겠어?
Are you OK with this?
Well, it makes me feel sad.. but..
슬프긴 하지만 뭐...
- 로스한테 얘기한거야
- 알았어
- talking to Ross
- I see
레이첼이 다른나라로 간다고?
Rachel moving to another contry? not being able to see her everyday? How, how can I be OK with this
매일 볼 수 없다고?
어떻게 내가 괜찮겠어?
그렇다고 우리가 뭘 어쩌겠어
쟤한텐 이 일이 정말 필요해
I know but what are we gonna do? She really needs this job
만약 랄프로렌에서
복직시켜준다면 받아들일까?
Do you think if.. ah.. if the Ralph Lauren people offered her her old job back, she would take it?
How's that gonna happen?
그런 일은 없을거야
이게 네 세가지 소원에
들어가는거냐?
Is this the best way to use one of your three magic wishes?
아냐, 내가 한번 레이첼 상사하고
얘기를 해봐야겠어
I don't know I could talk to her boss!
Yeah, I.. I met him at that Christmas party We.. we really hit it off
지난번에 크리스마스 파티에서 봤잖아
그날 우리 재밌게 놀았다고
오빠를 계속 '론'이라고
부르던 사람 말야?
You mean the guy who kept calling you 'RON'?
우리가 뭐 형제라도 되냐?
I didn't say we were brothers
FㆍRㆍIㆍEㆍNㆍDㆍS
10x15
The One Where Estelle Dies
10x15 The One Where Estelle Dies
[제 작]
코리아닷컴 프랜즈동호회 자막팀
[제 작] 코리아닷컴 프랜즈동호회 자막팀
[싱 커] 임욱재(sys_friends6@korea.com)
[해 석]
이상민(albireon@korea.com)
임의 수정 및 상업적용도의 사용을 금합니다
자막 피드백은 게시판을 이용해 주세요 (club.korea.com/friends)
[싱 커]
임욱재(sys_friends6@korea.com)
임의 수정 및 상업적용도의 사용을 금합니다
자막 피드백은 게시판을 이용해 주세요
(club.korea.com/friends)
피비~ 어떻게 생각하는지 얘기해봐
Hey, Phoebe. hey, tell me what you think
All right
우리가 웨스트체스터에 사기로 한
집의 옆 집이 매물로 나와서
The house next door to one that we're buying in Westchester just went on the market
난 한번 가보고 싶은데
챈들러는 싫대
I wanna take a look at it but Chandler doesn't
우리 내일이면 계약할거야
We close escrow tomorrow. so seeing other house can only confuse us
다른 집 보면 괜히
혼란스러울거 같다구
우린 그렇게 똑부러지지 못해서
쉽게 마음이 흔들린단말야
and we are easily confused. We are not very bright
우리집보다 좋으면 어떻게 해?
그냥 보기만 하는건데 어때
But what if that's better than the ours. Should we at least look?
피비, 어떻게 생각해?
What you think, Pheebs?
Well, I think that shirt makes you look like you should work at a BASKIN ROBBINS
내 생각엔 그 셔츠때문에 네가
베스킨라빈스 직원으로 보여
뭐 어쨌든...
Anyway
hey, isn't Joey's agent 'Estelle Leonard'?
'에스텔 레너드'가
조이 에이전트 아냐?
- 그런데?
- 죽었는데?
- yeah
- She died!
정말이야?
You kidding!
That's terrible
yeah, last Saturday
지난 토요일에 죽었는데?
Wow, she was the frist black man to fly solo across the Atlantic
에스텔이 대서양을 혼자
횡단 비행한 최초의 흑인이라는데?
oh, wait a minute. I read the wrong one
잠깐만... 내가 다른 사람 걸 읽었네
아, 그래
Oh yeah..
Yes, she was just an agent.
그냥 에이전트네
조이가 많이 슬퍼할거야
Joey is gonna be so upset
I know, he always wanna be the first black man to cross the Atlantic
그러게
조이는 항상 자기가 최초로 대서양을
횡단비행한 흑인이 되길 바랬으니까
조이한테 이 얘기를 할 순 없어
지금 일들 만으로도 힘들어하는데
We cannot tell Joey about this. He is already flipping out about everything that's changing
이 얘길 들으면 더할거야
this, this will push him over the edge
Seriouly you don't think we should tell him?
정말 얘기하지 말아야하나?
얼마간 만이라도...
Well, not for a little while. Let's just give him a few days to get used to everything else
며칠동안이라도 익숙해질
시간을 좀 주자고
What if he reads it in the paper
신문에서 읽으면 어떡해?
스누피가 찰리브라운한테
그 얘길 하지 않는한 괜찮을거야
Unless Snoopy says it to Charlie Brown, I think we're OK
무슨 일이시죠?
May I help you?
레이첼 그린 친군데요
Yeah. I'm a friend of Rachel Green's
2년 전 크리스마스파티에서
뵌 적이 있죠?
Uhm.. actually we met at the Christmas party about 2 years ago
그래요, 성함이 '돈'이였던가요?
Oh right..uhm.. Don?
비슷하죠, '론'입니다
Close. Ron!
Uh.. what can I do for you
무슨 일로 오신거죠?
Well.. I'm here to see if.. if.. you'll give Rachel her job back
혹시 레이첼을 복직시켜주실 순 없나
알아보려고 왔습니다
Ah..Did she ask you to come here and do this?
레이첼이 이렇게 해달라고
부탁하던가요?
Oh, no. At first I have to get you to agree, then we'll see if she wants to come back
아뇨, 일단 가능한지 알아보고나서
레이첼이 원하는지 알아봐야죠
Wow, that is tempting
그거 참 끌리는데요?
Look she loved her job here
레이첼이 자기 일을
얼마나 좋아했는데요
솔직히 레이첼만큼 그 일을
잘 하는 사람이 있나요?
Let's face it. You are not gonna find anyone who did it as well as she did it. isn't it true?
일을 잘하긴 했죠
She is good
정말 그랬나요?
Huh, I took a shot there
죄송하지만 해드릴 수 있는
일이 없네요
But I'm sorry. There's nothing I can do
Ah, it's not ture..There's.. nothing I want to do
솔직히 말해서 해드리고 싶은
마음이 없네요
네, 알겠습니다
I see
감사합니다
Thanks very much
당신 아들인가요?
Is this your son?
네, 이름이 '로스'에요
Yes, his name is Ross
왜요?
Why?
아뇨, 그냥 이름이
제 이름 '론'이랑 비슷해서요
Oh, nothing, it's just.. it's close to Ron
근데 아드님이...
공룡같은 걸 좋아하나요?
Does he..uh.. does little Ross like dinosaurs by any chance?
맨날 그 얘기만 하죠, 왜요?
Yeah, they're all he talks about. why?
저랑 같이 자연사 박물관에
가는 건 어떨까요?
How would HE like to come with me to the Museum of Natural History
박물관 문 닫은 뒤에
둘이서만 말이죠
after everyone else has left, just the two of us
원하는건 아무거나
만질 수 있게 해드리죠
and he can touch anything he wants
방금 제 말을 당신이 어떻게 들었을지
머리 속에 떠올랐어요, 좋지 않네요
I just heard it how you must have heard it. and that's not good
다시 설명할게요
전 고생물학자구요..
Let me start again. I'm a peleontologist
당신이 같이 가는거구요
You will be there with us
and the touching refers only to bones, fossils!
만지는 건 뼈만 얘기하는 겁니다
아니, 화석요!
정말 그렇게 할 수 있는 건가요?
You can really arrange that?
레이첼을 복직시켜주시기만 한다면
일은 다 된거죠
You let Rachel come back and it's done
Well.. I guess having Rachel back wouldn't be the worst thing in the world
레이첼을 복직시키는 게
그렇게 나쁜 일만은 아닌거 같네요
예! 고마워요, 정말 고마워요
Yes, yes. Thank you. This is great. Thank you so much
아드님은 평생 기억에 남을
시간을 보낼 거에요
I swear your kid is gonna have the time of his life
잘됐네요
사실 우리 로스가 좀 걱정되요
That's great. I worry about little Ross
He is always reading, he's collecting rocks and he's obsessed with dinosaurs
매일 책만 읽고, 돌을 수집하고
공룡에만 집착하고...
훌륭하게 자랄 거에요!
He will be fine
안녕, 피비
Hey, Phoebe
Hey, everything OK?
무슨 일 있어?
I'm just mad at my agent
그냥 에이전트한테 화가 나서
Estelle? Why?
에스텔한테? 왜?
TV 드라마에 내가 딱 적격인
역할이 하나 났는데
There's a part in a TV movie that I would be perfect for.
난 리스트에도 안올라 있잖아
변명거리라도 없기만해봐라!
And I didn't even be put up for it. She'd better have a good reason
아마 이유가 있을거야
I'm guessing she does
얘기를 좀 해봐야겠어
매번 이래
I want to hear it becuase she keeps doing this.
Well No! wait wait wait All right I.. I gotta go
기다려, 기다려
나.. 나 가야겠다
Just listen. Promise me that you will wait a minute before you call her
전화하기 전에 잠깐만
기다렸다 한다고 약속해줘
알았어, 근데 왜?
OK. why?
친구들간의 약속엔
이유가 필요 없는거야
Because a promise between friends means nerver having to give a reason
저 말 너무 좋은데?
I love that saying!
여보세요?
Hello
조이, 나 에스텔이야
Joey, It's Estelle.
지금 막 전화하려고 했는데
신기하네요
I was just gonna call you. That's wierd.
It's a little coincidental but believable
좀 우연적이긴 하지만
있을 만 하잖아
Listen. I'm sure you are wondering why I didn't get you an audition fot that TV movie
왜 TV드라마 오디션 받지 못했나
궁금해 하고 있지?
그래요
Yeah. Actually I am!
I guess I dropped the ball there. Whoopsie..
아무래도 내가 기회를
놓친 거 같아, 아뿔사~
그게 다에요? 요새 하는 일은
기회를 놓치는거 밖에 없어요?
That's it? You know, it seems like all you do lately is drop the ball.
Don't take that tone with me Who do you think you are?
그런 식으로 얘기하지마
네가 누구라고 생각하는거야?
앨런 레먼?
Allen Lemond-The First black man to fly solo across the Atlantic?
처음으로 대서양을 혼자
횡단 비행한 흑인?
아뇨, 당신은 내 에이전트인데
오디션 하나 못 따오잖아요
No no look All I'm saying is.. you are my Agent. OK? And you're not getting me any auditions and I'm tired of it
무슨 말이야?
What do you say?
내 말은... 더이상은 안되겠어요
당신 해고에요, 잘있어요
I'm saying that.. this isn't working for me anymore. OK? Estelle, you are fired. good bye
Man.. tough week for Estelle
에스텔한텐 참 힘든 한 주네
- 안녕?
- Hi
에마가 티라노 인형을
우리 집에 두고 갔네
Emma left her stuffed T-rex at my house. You know, she can't sleep without it
이거 없인 잠못자잖아
Well, she is sleeping now
에마 지금 자고있는데...
- 그거 그만 강요해
- 알았어
- Stop forcing that thing on her
- OK
참! 오늘 무슨 일이 있었는지 알아?
Oh, you are not gonna believe what happened to me today
랄프로렌에서 전화와서는
날 복직시켜주겠다고 하잖아
Ralph Lauren called and gave me my job back
정말?
Nooo
정말 이상하지 않아?
I mean, it was so wiredest thing. They fired me and then out of nowhere they just hire me back!
날 해고하고는 이유도 없이
복직시키겠다잖아
I mean that place must have been falling apart without me
나 없이는 회사일이 안돌아가나봐!
그럼 너 파리로 안가는거야?
So you are not going to Paris
아냐, 그래도 갈거야
No, I'm still going
Whoa.. wh.. wh... WHAT?
뭐라고?
Well.. When Louis Vuitton people found out that Ralph Lauren wanted me back
루이비통에서 랄프로렌이
복직 권유한 걸 알고는...
돈을 더 주겠다잖아
정말 대단하지 않아?
they offered me more money! Isn't that great?
Yay~~~!
Hi, We are buying the house next door and we were wondering if we could just take a look around
우린 옆집에 이사올 사람인데요
이 집을 잠깐 둘러볼 수 있을까요?
그럼요, 지금 다른 사람이 집을
보는 중이긴 하지만 둘러보세요
Oh sure I'm showing it to someone else right now. But please, look around
고마워요
Thanks
우린 지금 우리집을 두고
바람피는 거야
Feel like cheating on our house
기왕 바람피는거 우리집엔 없는게 많은
훨씬 젊고 멋진 집이랑 펴야하는거 아냐?
and if we're gonna cheat shouldn't it be with like a hot younger house and does stuff our house won't do?
우리집이 훨씬 더 좋네~
Ours is so much better
거실은 여기가 더 작아보이고
식당은 무슨 동굴같고
This livingroom is smaller, the dining room looks like a cave, huh, what a hole!!
완전 쥐구멍이야
어떻게 생각하세요?
So, what do you think?
정말 마음에 들어요!
LOVE IT!
벌써 사겠다는 사람이 한 사람 있구요
위층 여자분도 사려고 하는거 같은데요
Well, We already have one offer on it and I think the lady upstairs is going to make another one
우리 이웃이 될 수도 있겠다
어떤 사람들이에요?
They could be our neighbors. What are they like?
위층에 있는 여자는 굉장히 괜찮아요
남편하고 아이 둘이 있구요
Oh, the woman upstairs is very nice. She and her husband have two kids.
남편은 월스트리트에서 일하고
여자는...
He is on Wallstreet and she's on...
오...!
Oh~ My~ God!
맙... 소사!
그렇겠죠
sure
안녕, 조이
나랑 같이... 괜찮아?
Hey Joey, wanna come with me to... Are you OK?
에스텔 해고한게 좀 미안해서...
에스텔은 죽을거만 같을거야
Yeah.. I just feel bad about firing Estelle. It is gotta be killing her
그것 때문에 죽진 않을거야
'관동맥색전증' 때문이면 몰라두
No, that wouldn't kill her. Coronary embolism might
정말 힘들거야
내가 유일한 고객이었다구
Oh no.. She's gotta be taking it hard I was like her only client
나 말고 종이를 먹는 사람이 있긴 했지만
Except for this guy who eats paper
아마 그 사람은 먹는 돈이
버는 돈보다 많았을거야
And I'm guessing he eats more money than he makes
Look, I know she's not a great agent but she did stick with me for 10 years
그렇게 좋은 에이전트는 아니었지만
나랑 10년이나 같이 일했는데...
전화해서 다시 일하자고 해야겠어
I'm gonna call her and hire her again
NO NO NO You don't call her!
안돼 안돼 안돼~
전화하지 마!
에스텔이 전화하기를 기다려
You wait for her to call you
왜?
Why?
왜냐하면 인내는 이해의 지름길이니까
Because patience is the load to understanding
which is the key to a happy heart
행복을 찾는 열쇠라구
You blow me away
너무 감동적이야
All right, so promise you're gonna wait for her to call you
전화 올 때까지 기다린다고 약속한거다
I promise and that mean.. Never having to give a reason
약속할게, 왜냐하면...
친구 사이의 약속은
이유가 필요없으니까
세상 참 좁지?
What a small world!!
근데 왜 난 아직도 * 비욘세를 못만났지?
* 미국의 유명 여자 가수 겸 배우
And yet I never run into Beyonce!
서로 아는 사이세요?
You two know each other?
옛날 얘기죠
Oh, we go way back
모니카가 챈들러를
정직한 사람으로 만들기 전까지는
before Monica made an honest man out of him
챈들러가 내 사랑스런 머핀이었죠
Chandler used to be my~ little love muffin
너희들도 이 집 사려고 하는거야?
우리 입찰경쟁 해야하는거야?
So, are you guys thinking of getting this house too? Ooh.. Are we gonna have a bidding war?
경고하겠는데 날 쉽게 보지 말라구
I'd better warn you. I'm a toughie
하지... 하지 마
Don't.. Don't..
No, actually we are buying the house next door
사실 우리는 옆집을 살거야
왜... 왜?!
wh.. WHY?!
나도 왜 그랬는지 몰라!
I don't know why!
그럼 됐네, 살까말까 고민하고 있었는데
너희들이 옆집이라고? 그럼 사야지
Ooh, that decides it then.. I was on the fence but knowing that you two would be our neighbors. Ah, now we have to get it.
알렌, 나가서 금액조정이나 마무리하죠
Ellen, we're gonna talk numbers
어떻게 이런 일이!
This cannot be hanppening!
OK, the realtor said another made an offer. Maybe the Jenice's won't get it!
다른 커플도 가격 제시를 했다고 했잖아
제니스가 사지 못할 수도 있어
다른 커플이 살 수도 있다구!
Maybe the other couple will!
그런 일은 그 사람이
히틀러가 아닌 한 불가능해!
The only way to that is going to happen is if the other couple are the Hitlers!!
Ok ok.. all right, What if we get both houses. Huh? We can turn this house into a guest house!
그럼 우리가 두 집을 다 사는건 어때?
이 집은 손님용 집으로 쓰면 되잖아!
그거 좋은 생각인데
근데 반대하려는건 아닌데 말야
That's a great idea! And by the way I don't mean to sound distastful
but when did you start crapping money?
언제부터 돈을 그렇게
뿌려대기 시작한거야?
그럼 네가 생각을 좀 해봐
OK, you come up with an idea
좋아, 집을 계약할때까지 3시간 남았어
지금 빠지는거야!
All right, all right.. We still have 3 hours till escrow closes on our house. We can still get out!
하지만 저 집은 너무 좋단 말이야
But we love our house
제니스 옆집이라도 그렇게 좋아?
Will we love it so much with her next door?
And she's gonna be louder out here too! Just the crickets and 'Oh~ My~ God~ '
집 밖에서 떠들어댈거란 말야!
'오 맙소사~' 이러면서!
OK, but if we don't get this house, she's still gonna show up wherever we go.
하지만 우리가 이 집을 안사면
우리 가는데마다 계속 나타날거야
I mean, at least if she is here. It eleminates the element of surprise.
최소한 제니스가 여기 있음 만날때마다
깜짝 놀라진 않을거 아냐
그 놈의 세 단어 듣기만 해도 네 몸안
알이 튀어오르는거 같지 않냐구?!
I mean never again will you have to hear the three words that make your balls jump back up inside your body
무슨 수를 내야해
저 여자 옆집에 살 수는 없다구!
Well, we have to do something. We can't have her living next door.
저것도 그런데?
Huh, that does it too.
누구신가요?
Who is it?
접니다, 론이요
It's me. Ron.
Look, I.. I know Rachel turned you down. but...
레이첼이 제의를 거절한건 압니다
하지만...
I think there is a way you might be able to get her to come back.
레이첼을 붙잡을 수 있는
방법이 있는것 같은데요
This may surprise you but re-hiring fired-employees is not my main job.
놀라실지는 모르겠지만...
해고직원복직은 제 업무가 아닙니다
한번 들어나 보세요
더 많은 급여를 제의해보시는건 어때요?
Just here me out. How would you feel about offering her a raise.
별로 좋은 생각이 아닌 것 같네요
Not good. Ron
이걸 보시면 생각이 바뀔 겁니다.
이걸 아드님에게 주면 어떨까요?
Perhaps, I can persuade you. What if you can give your son
this genuine pterodactyl egg replica
진짜 익수룡 알...
같은 모조품을 말이죠
Wow... that's pretty cool..
거.. 멋진데요?
그럼 그렇게 해주시는거죠?
So.. we have a deal?
좋아요, 그렇게 하죠
OK. you got it.
좋아요!
YES! YES~!
이것 때문에 날 정말 좋아하겠는데요
This's gonna make me very popular
그럼요, 여자들은 그거에 환장하죠
Oh, believe me. The ladies, they love it.
전 아들 얘기 한건데요
I meant with my son
잘됐네요, 여자들은 사실
별로 안좋아해요
Good. 'cause the ladies not so much
조이, 나 엘지 부커에요
Joey. this is Al Zebooker
The guy who eats paper
종이 먹는 사람 기억나죠?
I'm sure you've heard that Estelle passed away
에스텔 죽었다는 얘기는 들었겠죠?
에스텔 추모회에 대해서 알려주려구요
서부예배당에서 내일 10시에요
I wanted to let you know there's a memorial for her at the westside chapel tomorrow at 10
참석할 수 있었으면 좋겠네요
Hope you can make it
이럴수가...
Oh my god
여보세요?
Hello
조이, 나 에스텔이야
Joey, It's Estelle
에스텔?
Estelle?
그래, 날 해고한 거에 대해 나쁜
감정은 없다고 얘기해주려 전화했어
Yeah, I wanted to call and tell you that there's no hard feelings for firing me
그래요...
OK..
나한테 전화를 하다니
믿을 수가 없네요
I just.. I can't believe you're calling me
잠깐 들릴까 생각하기도 했는데
Oh.. I didn't think I should just drop by
안돼요! 들리지 말아요
그러지 말아요!
No No No! Don't drop by. Don't drop by!
어쨌든 넌 할 일을 한거야
난 괜찮아
Anyway, you did what you had to do. I'm OK
Can I ask you something? hm..
뭐 좀 물어봐도 되요?
거긴 어때요?
What's it like there?
지낼만 해
It's all right
난 가야겠어, 일 잘 되길 빌어
넌 크게 성공할거야
Look kiddo. I gotta go. Good luck with the career. You're gonna be HUGE~
고마워요, 에스텔... 잘가요
Thanks for everything Estelle. Bye~
수신불가지역... 어쩐지...
"Out of Area" Boy, I'll say~
Well, I just talked to Sid. We're definitely putting in an offer on the house.
방금 남편이랑 얘기했는데
이 집 사기로 결정했어
And I'll bet we get it
분명히 우리가 살거야~!
히틀러네는 실망하겠네
The Hitlers will be so disappointed
All right. I gotta run. Tell Monica I say good bye. And..
나 가야겠다, 모니카한테
잘있으라고 전해줘, 그리고...
나중에 봐... 이웃사촌!
I'll see you later. Neighbor
잠깐! 너랑 여기 살게되서
너무 기쁘다는 걸 알아줘
Wait! I just want you to know that I'm so happy you're going to be here
오~ 나도 그래!
Oh~ me too..
왜냐하면! 이제 다시 헤어지기 전으로
돌아갈 수 있을테니까
BECAUSE! That way, we can pick up where we left off.
Huh?
뭐?
한시도 널 잊은 적이 없어
I never stopped loving you
Oh~ My..
그건 됐고..
Yeah yeah yeah..
널 원하고... 네가 필요하고...
널 갖고싶어
I want you, I need you, I must have you Janice Litman Goralnik Neihosenstein
챈들러, 지금 무슨 말을 하는거야?
Chandler, what are you talking about.
옆집에 살게되면 시드랑 모니카 모르게
매일 만날 수 있잖아!
Now that you live next door, we can be together everyday. Sid and Monica never have to know a thing
뭐라고 얘길해야할지 모르겠다..
I don't know what to say
물론 우리 사이에
뜨거운 감정이야 남아있지만
I mean.. obviously we have this heat between us
당연하지
Obviously..
난 남편을 사랑해, 그리고 너도
아내를 사랑한다는걸 알고...
But I love my husband and I know you love your wife
이 집을 사면 안되겠어!
I don't think we should get this house now
그러지마
불륜의 꿈을 앗아가지 말라구
Don't say that. Don't tangle the dream and take it away
우리 중에 한 사람은
마음을 굳게 먹어야 돼
Chandler, one of us has got to be strong
나도 이해해
I understand
하지만 이게 마지막으로 약한 순간이야
Although, maybe just one last moment of weakness
잘있어, 챈들러 빙~
Good bye, Chandler Bing
다신 내려오지 않겠구먼~
They are never coming down now
- 안녕?
- Hi! - Hi!
오늘 무슨 일이 있었는지 못믿을거야
You are never going to believe what happened to me today.
무슨 일인데?
What?
랄프 로렌에서 다시 전화가 와서는
봉급을 올려주겠데
Ralph Lauren called again and they offered me more money
- 정말이야?
- 그럼!
- They did! - Yes~
이상한건 말야, 젤너씨한테 전화와서는
복직시키기위해 무슨일이든 하겠다는거야
It was the weirdest thing. Zelner called me and he said we will do anything we can to get you back
그러면서 론이란 사람한테 감사하라네?
어느 부서 사람인지도 모르는데말야...
and that I should thank some "Ron". I don't even know what department that guy is in
그래서 어떻게 할거야?
So... what are you gonna do?
하겠다고 했지
Well, I took it
잘됐다, 그럼 뉴욕에 있겠구나
That's great. so you are staying in New York
- You are excited, right? - Yeah..
- 기쁜 거 맞지?
- 그럼...
You know, the money's great. It's certainly the easier choice.
돈도 많이 주고...
더 쉬운 선택이기도 하고
Right
그렇지
파리로 가길 정말
기대하고 있었지만 말야...
Yeah, you know, was I looking forward to going to Paris? Sure..
You know.. was I excited about working in the Fashion capital of the world? Ooh.. Absolutely
패션의 수도에서 일을 하다니
정말...
Yeah.. but you know, this is.. it's fine.. I'm fine going back to a job where I've pretty much gotten everything out of that I possibly can?
하지만 랄프로렌에서
다시 일하는 것도 좋아
내가 할 수 있는 일도
다 할 수 있고
Uhm, I hadn't no you..
나는 네가...
그렇게 파리 가는 걸
기대하고 있었는지 몰랐어
I had no idea you were so excited about Paris
Uhm I mean.. you said you were scared
겁난다고 했었잖아
Well.. yeah.. I mean, it was good scared though.. you know, like.. like when I moved to NY, scared
좋은 의미로의 겁이지, 내가 처음
뉴욕에 왔을때 겁먹었던 것처럼
아니면... 처음 에마를
가졌을때 겁났던 것처럼
or... when I found out I was gonna have Emma, scared..
근데 이것도 괜찮아
잘될거야
but.. this's fine.. this's gonna be good.
가라
You should go
뭐라고?
What?
네가 원하는게 그거라면 가라구
It's what you want, you should go
정말 그렇게 생각해?
You really think so?
정말이야
I really do
하지만 젤너씨한테 벌써
복직한다고 말해놨는걸?
But I already told Zelner that I would come back
그 사람도 이해할거야
I'm sure he'll understand
좋아, 좋아, 할거야!
파리로 갈거야!
All right! All right! I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna go to Paris
- 그래
- 그래!
- Yeah - Yeah!!
파리에 간다! 고마워, 로스
I'm going to Paris! Thank you Ross.
너무 기쁘다
I'm so happy!
그래, 나도 기뻐
Then I'm happy too..
다들 와주셔서 감사합니다
Thank you all for comming
우린 오늘 이자리에 훌륭한 에이전트였던
에스텔을 추모하기 위해 모였습니다
We are here today to pay respects to a wonderful agent
그녀는 참 아름다운...
and a beautiful woman
내면을 가졌었죠
inside..
그녀의 고객 중에 한사람으로써
몇마디 남기려고 합니다
As Estelle's only two clients, we would like to say a few words
내 연설문 어디갔죠?
Dude, where is my speech?
정말 재미있네요
엘지 부커였습니다!
That IS entertaining! Al Zebooker everybody.